Snail...not there, over here.
Honey, the snail won't go home.
Can you help?
Help me fix it.
Papa, I stopped it for you.
Come give me a hand.
Hurry up...
What now?
If the snail doesn't go home, pick it up
and put it back in the box.
Simple as that.
Why didn't I think of that?
Chung, you didn't need to stop it
with your hand.
If Papa doesn't know, you should.
Now I know.
OK...stop playing. Pack up your things.
Chi needs to shower
and go to the Day Activity Center (DAC).
OK!
Chung, come with me to collect the rent.
It's so hot,
I don't know why country folks
don't trust banks.
Why must we collect cash?
We've been doing this for decades.
Can't expect grand aunt to go to the bank.
You always sit around
and do nothing all day.
When we ask you to do something...
Chi!
Chi...are you OK?
Chi...
Papa, are you OK?
I'm fine.
How many times did I tell you?
Don't make him put things away.
Don't let him shower himself.
He might slip and fall.
See? He's almost hurt.
He said he's fine. Will you relax?
You never let him do anything.
Now he can't do anything.
He has the IQ of an 8-year-old.
What do you expect him to do?
You're his wife,
you're supposed to look after him for life.
Exactly! I'm his wife.
I'll decide for him, not you.
I'm his mother and your mother-in-law.
Why can't I decide for him?
I won't let you bully Chi.
I'm not talking to you.
Chung, let's go
before she starts calling you a retard
and wants to run your life.
I'm not finished. You abandon Chi again.
Where are you going?
Out. And it's none of your business.
Of course it is! I forbid it.
Out of my way!
You...
Grandma...are you OK?
Honey, don't do that...
You'll be struck by thunder!
Mom...
What's the racket now?
She should be struck by thunder...
Kin-kwok, look! She had the nerve to hit me!
If you don't teach her,
I have no place in this house.
She only tried to break away and
hit you by mistake.
I told you to butt out of their affairs.
But you wouldn't listen.
She doesn't know her place.
You should discipline her, not blame me.
Even her son is an adult.
You're asking for trouble if you
keep meddling.
That's because Chi was born this way.
I won't let anyone bully him.
Whoever bullies him will answer to me.
Will you stop making such a racket at home?
Ping, Chung, let's go to the village office.
Kin-kwok...
Chief!
Mrs. Cheung...
Uncle Tung, Brother Fa, Grandpa Fat,
Mrs. Tsang, Auntie Chu, Uncle Shun,
good morning...
Morning...
Good boy!
Why is there a new plaque?
(Noble and Venerable)
Your Grandpa helped raise money
for Auntie Nam's medical expenses.
Uncle Nam was very pleased.
He sent this plaque in recognition of
his good deed.
That's right!
Nam didn't have to. It was nothing.
Chung, you've been coming here a lot lately.
Exactly!
He's helping out.
He's old enough to help out.
He's so good looking, just like his Mom.
Luckily he takes after his Mom
and not his Dad.
I want to be like Papa too.
Chi is quite smart.
He picked such a good wife
who gave him a good son.
Father...I have invoices for you to sign.
Bring them here.
We'll get out of your way...
Bye!
Chung!
Yes?
Bring me those two cartons in the storeroom.
We'll need them when
we worship our ancestors.
OK!
Next to the printer...
Chief!
What?
Kwun is waiting for you outside.
I'll go out.
Watch your step.
Hi, Kin-kwok.
What's up? Need any help?
Let's have dinner.
Godfather!
Hi, Chung!
You look so much better.
Putting the crystal cluster in your room
is good for you.
You have a different aura.
Really?
Just do as I say.
Call me if you need anything, OK?
I'll help you.
She roughed you up?
Daughters-in-law nowadays are ferocious.
I won't put up with it anymore.
I will have it out with Kin-kwok tonight.
He indulged the daughter-in-law
and she had the nerve to hit me.
What if she starts hitting Chi?
I won't let her bully us.
Master likes her because she's helpful.
So what?
Before she married into this family,
I took care of matters at
the village office.
I will fight her.
I will show her who's in charge.
I don't mind having it out with Kin-kwok.
Mom, I took a shower.
Look at you, your hair is wet.
Dry off the body or you'll catch a cold.
You should let me bathe you.
Honey said it's better to do it myself.
Don't listen to her.
Why didn't you put on boxers?
I told you to put on boxers.
This one is tight and stuffy.
You're sweaty and will have rashes.
Chau!
It wasn't me.
Madam Ping said this is better.
Honey said this is more comfortable.
You listen to everything she says.
What is her intention?
She always opposes me.
Chung!
Grandpa and I have something to do.
Remember last time you collected rent
from great aunt?
This time, after your great aunt,
can you collect the rent from someone else?
Yes. You taught me.
Hurry up, OK?
OK!
Ping, you taught him well.
Chung is smarter than Chi,
but he still can't compare
to ordinary folks.
He has limited intelligence.
You must teach him to be more independent.
Don't spoil him like Han did.
I know.
Sorry!
I missed the bus waiting for you.
Now I must take a taxi.
Are you paying for that?
Sorry, I'm really sorry!
I'll be on time next time.
Wait...because of the No. 8 typhoon signal
a few days ago,
the windowsill was leaking,
and all my things got wet.
You should pay for the damages.
I lost over $10k because of it.
I'll dock that from this month's rent.
What?
You must pay your rent on time.
It cannot be used to offset anything.
I'm the owner Cheung Kin-kwok's counsel.
The leaking of the windowsill
was a condition you were aware of
when you signed the lease.
You were in a hurry to open your shop
and refused to let the owner repair it.
It was clearly stated in the lease
you're responsible for any loss incurred
because of it.
But since you made it sound so serious,
the leaking problem may affect
the structure of the shop.
I will suggest to the owner
to bring in professionals to inspect
the premises
and decide whether anything
had to be fixed
or it was the result of improper use.
It should be OK if we don't have
another typhoon.
Look, I'm in a hurry.
Here.
Bravo, Sis!
Luckily, I ran into you.
Or else she's likely to scare you
and you'd let her deduct money
from the rent
and we'd be in trouble.
I know.
Some people pick on targets to bully.
Next time you run into a tenant like that,
tell them you can't make decisions.
You'll need to call Grandpa, OK?
Can I call you?
Definitely not!
I don't want to get involved.
I'm only doing this for you.
Also, cut your bad habit of being late.
Or you'll give people an excuse
to use that against you, understand?
Remember we're seeing a movie
the day after tomorrow?
Don't be late.
You're right...I won't be late.
Let me get that for you.
Good boy!
I'll let you in on a secret.
What?
I didn't count the money.
You didn't?
You're dead if Grandpa found out!
Father, I drew a snail. Is it pretty?
Yes...
I'm very tired. Go play over there.
I need to rest.
Grandpa! Papa!
Hey!
You came home together?
Chung B, you're home?
I saw a tenant bullying Chung,
and I rescued him.
Come draw with me...
Here? Use yellow.
Would you like a candy?
Yes! Sis stood up for me.
Really?
No, thanks.
If you want to draw better, do it upstairs.
Upstairs is even better?
Yes!
OK, I'll go upstairs.
I...
Chung, don't do those childish things
with your Papa anymore.
Try to learn from your sister.
Make yourself useful, OK?
Tai-di, you're a smart girl.
You're good at school and at work.
But what a shame you're a girl.
You will get married someday,
you can't take over the family.
Try to make time for your brother
so he can be smart like you, OK?
Make him useful, understand?
Teach him. I'm going upstairs.
Sis, if only I'm half as capable as you are,
I'd be very happy already.
My Boss wanted to send me overseas
and work for a law firm we have
a joint venture with.
I guess it won't be happening now.
Why?
I need money.
Didn't you hear what Grandpa said?
When I have money,
I'll give you money to go to school.
For as long as you like.
When you have money?
You didn't have much schooling,
how can you make money?
You can barely feed yourself.
Don't look down on me.
If I win the lottery,
I won't share it with you.
Oh, I'm so scared. I'm begging you...
If you win $20, give me $1, OK?
What a brat!
Pack your Papa's things.
Right!
Chau!
Yes?
No bird's nest today?
No more.
Why didn't you get more?
You knew Chi needs bird's nest every day
for nutrition
and to keep his mind active.
Madam Ping said Master Chi doesn't need it.
She said bird's nest has the same
nutritional value as tofu,
there's no need to waste money on it.
Follow me.
What?
Why didn't you buy bird's nest?
Because it's useless.
What are these?
Vitamins.
Chi has been eating bird's nest
since he was little.
Who says it's useless?
If he has been eating since he was little
and he's still like this, it's useless.
Vitamins is what he needs.
This is the doctor's idea, not mine.
Nothing he eats can make him smarter.
He should try to do more things
to make him more independent.
You can cut back on anything,
but not Chi's expenses.
I also cut your fish maw.
You're too old, it'll give you indigestion
or you'll get stomachache or feel gloated.
You'll only waste money to see a doctor.
Are you cursing me?
You can't stop until I say so.
Chau, get me fish maw and bird's nest.
That's beyond Chau's grocery money.
But you can buy it with your own money.
I won't stop you.
But this is not included
in our grocery money.
Madam Han!
I've had enough.
I want to supervise the household expenses.
Please don't start any trouble.
We're too old to argue.
You don't need the hard work.
She fights me on everything.
She's a thorn in my flesh.
She's a real piece of work.
She's young and is bound to
do things differently.
The house is newer and more stylish.
She kept the house clean and tidy
and took good care of Chi and Chung.
What more do you want?
Since you put her in charge of
the household expenses,
she's becoming more domineering.
You saw the way she talked to me.
Now she wants to cut the tonic
for Chi and me.
She made Chi wear those cheap underwear
while she's getting all dressed up.
I bet she embezzled the money.
I want to oversee the
household expenses again.
Will you stop causing trouble?
I will check the books by month end. Relax!
Check? How? By turning a blind eye?
Let me ask you...you know English?
Can you type or turn on the computer?
Listen, you handpicked Ping yourself.
She was willing to marry Chi
and ran a tight ship around the house.
You should count your blessings.
Stop complaining.
If she won't listen, just live with it, OK?
I'm tired. I'll go shower.
If I wasn't worried about getting old
and no one would look after my son,
(21 years ago)
I would never have made this wrong move
and brought this jinx home.
Mrs. Cheung!
You made this for Chi?
I always pack lunch.
I know Cheung Wang-chi likes braised pork
with preserved vegetables
so I made a bit more for him.
I'm sorry, he ate your lunch.
We're sharing, right?
Yes!
Mrs. Cheung, why don't you sit down?
I'll get you some water.
Good.
Chi, do you like Miss Leung?
Shall I bring her home
and let her take care of you?
You want that?
Yes!
Miss Leung, thanks for looking after Chi
for the past two years.
This is something for you.
You have given me enough during
the festivals.
I can't accept something so expensive.
Please take it back.
Small diamonds like these are
not worth much.
I bought something for myself and
got this for you.
Thank you, Mrs. Cheung.
Taking care of Chi is very easy.
He's fun to be around with.
I remember you told me
your family is in debt
and you must work a few jobs to pay it off.
I think you and Chi get along very well.
You know he only has the IQ
of an 8-year-old.
But he's kind and good-tempered.
Since you've been looking after him,
why don't you marry him?
Then you won't have to look after
anyone else.
It never crossed my mind...
I will clear your family debt for you
and give you a considerable sum
as betrothal money.
You'll be rid of the debt
and live a worry-free life.
But there's no hurry. You can think it over.
I thought with her watching over Chi,
she can relieve my heavy burden
and take care of Chi for the rest
of his life.
She was doing so well at first.
But she became a different person
after Chung was born.
She doesn't care about Chi anymore.
Chi!
Ouch, Mom...
She gradually got out of hand.
Now, I still had to worry about Chi.
That woman completely ignored me.
Honey?
What now?
Kiss kiss...
Out of my way. I'm not in the mood.
Honey, kiss kiss...
I told you...
I'll teach you to say something.
I want you to say it to your mother.
If you can do it, we'll kiss kiss, OK?
OK!
I don't like bird's nest.
Don't make it anymore.
I'll take vitamins instead.
I don't like bird's nest.
Don't make it anymore. I'll...
So long, I can't remember.
Can you remember now?
I don't like bird's nest.
Don't make it anymore.
I'll take vitamins instead.
Good!
Remember to tell your mother.
What now? I want to take a shower.
Together.
When did we do that together?
You won't listen to me?
Then I'm not talking to you.
Don't forget those lines.
I don't like bird's nest.
Don't make it anymore.
I'll take vitamins instead.
There you are...please put that in here.
Take that away.
This is my room. You can't have it.
I bought that. Please put it inside.
Take that away.
Don't you dare take my room.
You're not in charge around here.
I didn't take anything.
Father said I can have it.
I said no!
Settle this between yourselves.
We'll wait outside.
Take it away...
No...
I have had enough of you!
You have no say around here.
I want you to leave.
I'd like to see you try.
Your husband, your son and
your grandson need me.
Did you ask them?
Nam, say something.
Is she out of line or what?
Don't be upset. Let's wait for Kwok.
Kin-kwok, I'm glad you're home.
She turned my mahjong room into a bedroom.
Will you shut up? I'm not feeling well.
I need to go lie down.
You've been drinking already?
I'm not feeling well. My head hurts.
My chest feels tight. Just be quiet.
How can you give her the room?
What about me?
Father said he's not feeling well.
Leave him alone.
Father, I'll help you upstairs.
Quit your act.
Because you indulge her
she's pushing her luck.
She's never home, she neglects Chi
and is always contradicting me.
I won't have it. One of us will have to go.
If she doesn't, I will.
What do you say?
Shut up!
Father!
Kin-kwok...don't scare me!
Father...
I'll get an ambulance.
Well? Master Kwok!
Kin-kwok!
Father!
(Ancestor Cheung Kin-kwok)
Madam Han, don't think too much.
Have some water and don't be too sad.
Chung B!
Yes?
Where is Dad, now that he's dead?
Can he still see my draw?
It's your drawing.
I don't think Grandpa can see.
He should be in the sky.
They say people become stars when they die.
There are so many...Which one?
Let's look for one that's blinking.
That one should be Grandpa.
That one is blinking! Is that Dad?
Yes, it should be.
Dad is so far away,
who's in charge when something happens?
Hurry up! Everyone is waiting.
Honey!
For future family meetings,
I don't want anyone to be late.
As soon as Father is gone,
you assume you're the head of the family.
I need to set things straight.
Before the lawyer reads Kin-kwok's will,
I'm taking over the family.
I trust even after the will is read,
things won't be any different.
Kin-kwok may be gone,
all expenses and allowance
will be the same.
But I noticed something questionable
about the household expenses.
Why are we $20K short every month?
Ping, you need to explain.
Father already went through the books.
He found nothing wrong.
Are you saying Kin-kwok took the money?
Impossible!
He gave you a separate allowance,
he won't dock it from the
household expenses.
He was partial towards you.
Don't use him as your excuse.
Every dollar you spent
must be accountable and necessary.
You better explain.
You're welcome to find out for yourself.
Did you buy that diamond ring?
I helped Father with this and that
and followed him here and there.
I deserved a salary for it.
I bought it with my own money.
Your salary can't afford that.
You bought a lot of jewelry
over the past two years.
Did you take money from the family?
You better cough it up.
I deserved everything I had.
I have a clear conscience.
I'm hungry. Why don't I treat you
to a dim sum lunch?
Good. I'm hungry too. I want dim sum.
Grandma, let's have dim sum.
Mom, I want dim sum...
Fine! I'm giving you a week
to make up for the missing money.
Maybe it won't take a week.
In a few days, things may be turned around.
You'll be begging me instead.
What does she mean turn around?
Did she find a rich sugar Daddy
to pay for her fancy clothes?
Tai-di?
What?
You're never home.
When you go out, did you notice
people your Mom hang out with?
Or have you seen her out there?
No. I never butt into your affairs.
Whenever I ask you...
Auntie Chau...
I can change the sheets myself.
Chau, I want my sheets changed.
Come to my room.
Madam Han!
That wench said just now...
In less than a week, things will be
turned around
and I would beg her.
What does that mean?
You asked her to pay back
the money in front of everyone,
I think she was just bluffing.
She's capable of anything.
I think she must have done something.
Maybe not.
When you clean her room or do her laundry,
did you find anything suspicious?
That reminds me, yes!
I found two invoices and a deposit slip.
One invoice is for gold jewelry.
I found these in her pocket when
I took her clothes to the dry cleaner.
See?
She deposited $30K cash into her account?
She doesn't have that much money.
I'm thinking if someone out there
gave her the money.
You think so too?
Recently, she's always going out.
Did she go out to meet men?
Maybe what I saw was true.
But it can't be...
What is it? Tell me.
A few months ago, I saw Madam Ping
go out all dressed up.
Right before she left,
she pulled out her phone
and something that looked like condoms
fell out onto the ground.
She quickly picked it up
and put it back into her bag.
Why didn't you tell me?
I only took a quick glance.
I wasn't sure if I really saw it.
This is a very serious charge.
I shouldn't shoot off my mouth.
How dare she made a cuckold out of my son!
No wonder when I asked Chi...
...he gave me weird answers...
Your wife is inside, why don't you go in?
No. She's changing. She won't let me see.
She won't let you see her change?
What do you do at night?
Sleeping.
Anything else?
Sing, draw, play with the snail...
and sleep.
No kiss kiss?
Yes, only if I behave.
Otherwise, no kiss kiss.
When was the last time you did this?
What is that?
Oh dear!
They haven't?! Oh dear!
Did Master Chi piss her off?
She leaves Chi behind in the house
while she goes out all dressed up.
She must have a lover.
That's why she won't let Chi touch her.
She said I'll be begging her.
Is it because she'll run off with her lover?
I'll have to beg her to stay
and look after Chi and Chung?
Mom, what are you doing?
You look like you're moving.
Didn't you see Grandma's attitude
towards me this morning?
I don't think I can live here anymore.
Grandpa used to put in a good word.
But now?
We're leaving once we get the money.
No. What about Papa? You're leaving him?
I'll listen to you.
Grandpa always said the family
must stick together.
Quiet! Don't wake Papa.
Shouldn't you be in bed?
We don't know what will happen.
We'll decide later.
OK!
Good night, Papa.
Folks, you all have a copy of
an attachment,
listing the assets of the late
Mr. Cheung Kin-kwok
including this mansion in Ko Cho Village
which is worth $30M
and other land, shops and investments
worth around $70M.
His total assets are worth $100M.
According to Mr. Cheung's will,
he left everything to one person,
his grandson, Mr. Cheung Siu-chung.
No way! Are you sure?
What about me and my son?
It's written in his will.
But there's also one condition,
Mr. Cheung Siu-chung must wait till
he's 21 years old
before he can inherit the estate.
When I'm dead, I'll leave you the mansion.
That creep lied to me.
But at least he left everything to Chung.
Chung is my son, at least I got something.
Unlike her, who has nothing.
Mr. Lam, can I turn it down?
This is old Mr. Cheung's last wish.
He wants you to decide what to do
with the money.
He believed you would look after the family
and would know what to do.
He let him decide what to do with $100M?
He has limited intelligence.
The money is as good as gone.
Thank you, Mr. Lam. I'll walk you out.
I don't understand why Kin-kwok
would put that in the will.
Chi and I have nothing.
It must be you.
You did something to make him
leave a will like this.
Father was always keen on his bloodline.
Leaving everything to Chung wasn't so bad.
I won't get any of it either.
Relax! You'll live your remaining years
in comfort.
It really doesn't matter.
Chung is the only male heir.
He'll take care of all of you.
It should be a well thought out decision
by Grandpa.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Mom, why are you so angry?
I told you things may be turned around.
I guess even Father had no intention
to put you in charge.
Why? Not resolved?
Go to Hell and ask him about it.
What did you say?
Neither of us will get the money.
There's no need to argue.
Father was so thoughtful.
Chi, time to go to the DAC.
I don't want to stay and talk.
Here...carry this.
If Madam Ping found out
we're searching her room,
she'll throw a fit.
She took Chi to the DAC.
She won't be home soon.
We must find proof of her
taking on a lover.
Even if we find any proof, what can we do?
Master Kwok gave everything to Chung
and Chung listens to Madam Ping.
She'll eventually get the money.
If Chung is not a Cheung,
Kin-kwok's estate will go to an outsider.
I don't care if we go to court,
I must get the money back.
Look at this!
This is a hotel keycard.
So?
She kept a regular room at a hotel
to rendezvous with her lover.
She cheated on Chi!
Look at this!
September 15?! That was the day
Kin-kwok died.
This is a couple package.
She had a tryst that morning.
She had no shame.
No wonder she had money for the jewelry.
She had a sugar Daddy.
What should we do now?
We must find this man
and see if Chung is Chi's son.
Chung, I always loved you like a son
and I always will. Don't worry.
I need to pee.
I'll go with you.
No, I'm OK.
Be careful.
Don't be too heartbroken.
That hotel is near Nam's office.
I think so.
But maybe not.
The day Master Kwok died,
I think they came back together.
They came from their tryst.
Master Nam is family, he wouldn't dare.
I thought it was weird
he asked to be Chung's godfather back then.
Nam doted on Chung since he was little.
Now that you mentioned it, it's probable.
Is it possible Chung is Nam's son?
Ouch! Why did you pull my hair? It hurts.
Exactly! What's wrong with you?
Why did you pull out his hair?
Why? Does it break your heart?
What are you saying?
Your heart is aching for your lover? I know.
What lover? You better explain yourself.
I know he's Chung's father, not Chi.
Are you crazy? Watch your mouth!
Be careful with what you say, Cousin.
Is there a misunderstanding?
I know all about you two.
Chung is not a Cheung,
He's your illegitimate son.
Grandma, calm down.
I'm definitely Papa's son.
I need your hair for a DNA test.
I suggest you stop doing this.
Chung is definitely a Cheung.
Why? You have something to hide?
Can't show your face when
the results come out?
I must expose you.
I want the world to know
the shameful thing you did.
Fine! You want to know? I'll tell you.
You're right. Chung is not Chi's son.
You finally admit it!
You lied to us for over 20 years.
How vicious of you!
I said Chung is not Chi's son.
But I didn't say he's not a Cheung.
What are you trying to say?
Listen carefully.
Chung is my son with your husband,
my father-in-law.
Cheung Siu-chung is Cheung Kin-kwok's son.
Here's the DNA report. See for yourself.
How do I know if this is real?
You want to know?
Go in and pull a hair from Father
and compare that with Chung's.
Chung is part of the Cheung family.
He deserves what he got.
Last time you asked me where
the jewelry came from.
They were from your husband.
And the missing $20K every month?
That was a gift from him. Happy now?
He said you two had things to do.
And you went to a tryst in a hotel.
Yes, we came back together that day.
He told you he wasn't feeling well.
Why? Because he took medication
and was too aroused.
But you badgered him with questions
and gave him a stroke.
You killed him.
You killed my husband.
You messed with him and cheated on Chi.
I'm the victim here.
You couldn't please your husband.
I had to pick up after you.
It was your premeditated plan
to marry into this family and
steal our money.
That's why you had the DNA test,
you cheap whore!
I was worried once Father is dead,
you'll frame me for something
and send me away.
Of course I had to do the DNA test
to protect Chung.
Chung is part of the family and
deserves a share of the fortune.
Cheung Kin-kwok, get up!
You won't get away with what you did...
Madam...
He's dead...don't do this...
Cousin, show some respect for the dead.
Get up...
Madam Han!
You have guests. Are you ready?
Coming!
Madam, guests are arriving. Stop crying.
Do your crying at home.
Father was well respected.
You better get this show on the road.
Honey, what's going on?
Guests are arriving. Let's go outside...
What's done is done, about Master Kwok,
don't be so upset.
Take it easy and mind your health.
Don't remind me of that creep!
Grandma, please don't be angry.
It's bad for you.
Have some honey lemon with tangerine peel.
Stop calling me that. I'm not your Grandma.
You're the illegitimate son my husband
had with that tramp.
I know what Mom did was wrong.
But can you not be angry with me?
Get out! I don't want to see you!
Don't come into my room anymore.
And stop calling me Grandma.
Chung, stop calling her Grandma.
It's jarring to her ears.
Try not to show up before Madam Han.
You're a thorn in her flesh.
Run along now...
Chung B...what's wrong?
Are you upset?
Papa...no, I shouldn't call you Papa.
I should not...I don't know
what to call you.
Why? You're my son.
No. Our relationship is gross.
What?
I don't know what to say.
Chi...
Go play by yourself.
I hate you. Why did you do it?
Chung...
Listen to me.
Calm down and listen to me.
It's not what you think.
I'm the victim here.
Back then, I had to pay a family debt,
that's why I married into this family.
People sit in judgment over me
and accused me of marrying Chi for money.
I was under a lot of pressure and
I was unhappy.
Luckily Father was highly respected
and he was very nice towards me, but...
Father, what are you doing here?
Father...no...
I felt dirty and wanted to kill myself.
But soon I found out
I was pregnant with you.
I didn't want to lose you.
I had nowhere to go,
so I was forced to stay.
I put up with the pain and shame
to raise you.
I don't want to know...
Stop! I don't want to listen...
Don't say it...
Chung!
(Two days after Chung left home)
Why didn't Chung B come home?
He left me a message telling me
he wants to be alone.
Don't worry about him.
Chung B's birthday is coming up.
I want to celebrate with him.